<metadata>
  <title><![CDATA[ Lightweight Lua]]></title>
  <threadUrl><![CDATA[https://ftlmultiverse.boards.net/thread/115/mv-5-less-managable-crew]]></threadUrl>
  <author><![CDATA[ Limrix ]]></author>
  <version><![CDATA[ 0.15.2 ]]></version>
  <description>
<![CDATA[
# Lightweight Lua
A library of several useful functions.  Aims to make lua scripting less of a pain.
Categories:
    Logging, Crew, Geometry, Point, Angle, Events, Control Flow

### Lightweight 3D
A simplistic 3d rendering library, lw3.  This is what Omen in FFFTL uses.

### UI Library
Do all sorts of things with a whole bunch of visual elements.  Used in Grimdark Expy.  Includes:
    Buttons, Scroll bars, text boxes, and more!

### Stable Time
A library that takes care of normalizing onTick logic across all fram

### Event Broadcaster
Informs you of when things happen that are annoying to track.  Supports:
    Crew death animation started, crew death animation finished, crew cloned, hangar entered, player variables loaded.

### Meta and Player Variable Structure
Gives an object-oriented way of registering persistent variables.  This keeps track of how many of a kind of object are stored, and what properties those objects have.

### Safe Script
    A wrapper around calls to script that allows you to change or remove the callback.
    Required for runtime hotswapping of code so that you can deregister the previous iteration.

### Status Effects Library
Apply statuses to crew, such as bleed, corruption, and confusion. Used in Grimdark Expy.

### Keybinds
Gives an easy interface for registering key press events, including combinations of modifier keys.

### XML Generation
Lua scripts for creating the xml required for animations and lab upgrades.  Leave suggestions if you think I should add something here.

### Self-Indexing List
For when you want members to implicitly know their index.

### Doubly Linked List
A basic doubly linked list implementation.

### Crew Change Observers
Register to know when your ship's crew changes

### Teleport Status Observers
Register to know if any crew is teleporting

### Blood
Not a library, this is a toggleable feature that adds crew-specific bloodstains on death.

### Clone Orders
This is another toggleable feature, this time making your crew go do something when they clone in instead of standing there.

## Requirements
[Multiverse](https://ftlmultiverse.boards.net/)

[Brightness Particles](https://ftlmultiverse.boards.net/thread/109/library-brightness-particles)
]]>
  </description>
</metadata>
